Bruno Justino Garcia Praciano Résumé



- △ | Brasília-DF, Brazil
- **+**55 (61) 98355-0909
- □ bjpraciano@gmail.com
- i www.lasp.unb.br

SUMMARY

In this résumé you can find that my expertise is focused on machine learning techniques specially in text mining. I also have a deep interest in other types of machine learning applications. I have been recently working on face recognition and peer to peer networks in my actual position. My background also includes full stack development and biomedical engineering product development.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

April 2019 – Present: Legal Labs Artificial Intelligence Activities:

- Intelligence platform mass process based on prediction
 - TensorFlow
 - Pytorch
 - Spark
 - Python
 - Natural Language Processing
 - WebCrawler

October 2017 – Present: Universal Internet of Things Laboratory Activities:

- Implementation of face recognition using IoT
 - Face Recognition
 - Deep Learning
 - OpenCV
 - Python
 - RaspberryPI
- Peer to Peer Network to IoT devices
 - Sockets
 - Chord Network

September 2017 – August 2018: **Robotic Process Automation Developer at DOZE** Activities:

- Robotic Process Automation
 - WDG Automation
 - Automation Anywhere
 - Scrapy and Selenium
- Customer Service
 - Marketing
 - Direct Contact with clients

June. 2016 - September 2017: CTO at Eduqc.com

- Team Management with Agile with Scrum
- Full Stack development
 - Laravel, Python, Javascript, Vue
 - SQL, AWS

Jan. 2015 - April. 2017: Researcher at Biomedical Engineering Laboratory - UnB.

EDUCATION

March 2019 – Present: **Master of Science in Electronics and Automation Engineering** University of Brasília (UnB)

April 2013 – December 2018: **Computer Engineer Bachelor Degree** University of Brasília (UnB)

COMMUNICATION SKILLS

PORTUGUESE Native speaker

ENGLISH Oral and written: advanced

GERMAN Oral and written: basic

SPANISH Oral and written: basic with good understandability due to similarity

SOFTWARE SKILLS

GOOD LEVEL Python, R, Sci-kit Learn, TensorFlow, NLP, Javascript, Vue, C, Matlab,

PHP, HTML, CSS, LTEX, Linux, Docker, SQL

INTERMEDIATE React, Node, Django, MongoDB

RESEARCH INTERESTS

Artificial Intelligence, Internet of Things, Data Mining

SELECTED VOLUNTEER ACTIVITIES

President and founder of the first IEEE Vehicular Technology Society (VTS) chapter in Brazil.

Founder and Publication Chair of the Workshop on Communication Networks and Power Systems (WCNPS) in 2017 and 2018.

SELECTED PUBLICATIONS

[1] **B. Praciano**, J. P. C. L. da Costa, J. P. A. Maranhão, J. B. Prettz, R. T. de Sousa Jr. and F. Mendonca, Spatio-Temporal Trend Analysis of the Brazilian Elections based on Twitter Data, 2018 IEEE International Conference on Data Mining Workshop (ICDMW), Singapore,